

# ESAD BORAN

Computer Engineer

## PROFILE

I am a 3rd year Computer Engineering student at Hacettepe University. I learn Python, Java and C++ languages in detail and develop small projects using these languages. I want to improve myself on Web Framework, Data structures and Artificial Intelligence. I think I have the ability to work and research on any subject.

## CONTACT



0 553 463 91 19



esatsuphi@gmail.com



linkedin/esadboran2018



github/esadboran



ANKARA - İZMİR

## LANGUAGES

- Turkish(Native Language)
- English (B2 Level)
- German (A1 Level)

#### **EDUCATION**

HACETTEPE UNIVERSITY (2018 - 2024)

Computer Science - 3. Year

• GPA: 3.10 / 4

SUPHİ KOYUNCUOĞLU ANATOLIAN HIGH SCHOOL (2014 - 2018)

• GPA: 89.27 / 100

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

ODAKGIS | September 2018 - December 2018
Volunteer Internship

- Linux learning experience with an Information Security Specialist
- Having good experiences with Computer Engineer software developer working in Python and Java languages

SiSBiM | June 2022 - July 2022 Internship

- I learned Html, Css, Javascript for web programming
- I developed cloned **Django** projects such as Netflix, Blog, Instagram, and then we created web pages with the team I was with, and we also fixed the errors in our webpage.

#### SKILL

- Languages: Python 5  $\bigstar$ , Java 4 $\bigstar$ , C++ 3 $\bigstar$ , C# 3 $\bigstar$ , SQL 3  $\bigstar$ , C.2 $\bigstar$
- Web Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Web Framework: Django
- Knowledge: Machine Learning, TensorFlow,
- Data Analysis, Data Structures, Object Orented Design, Algorithm, Latex, Git
- Mcrosoft: Word, Excel, Powerpoint

(40+ HOURS) COMPLETE JAVA DEVELOPER

HACKKERANK BASIC PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

### **CERTIFICATE**

**COURSE FROM ZERO** 

O <u>Türk Telekom &amp; TRAI Veri Bilimi Analitiği</u> <u>Practicum</u>	January 2023
INTRODUCTION TO TENSORFLOW FOR ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE, MACHINE LEARNING, AND DEEP LEARNING	July 2022
PROGRAMMING FOR EVERYBODY (GETTING STARTED WITH PYTHON)	February 2022
(40+ HOURS) PYTHON   ADVANCED PROGRAMMING FROM ZERO	2021-2022
(AO+ HOURS) COMPLETE IAVA DEVELOPED	2022

2022